<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<CommunityApplications>
  <Profile>
# YAHLP - Yet Another HomeLab Portal Templates

Unraid container templates for YAHLP (Yet Another HomeLab Portal), a comprehensive reverse proxy and unified media server dashboard for homelab environments.

## What's Included

This repository contains 4 pre-configured Unraid container templates for different deployment scenarios:

- **yahlp-private-basic.xml** - Private mode (HTTP) with HTTP Basic Authentication
- **yahlp-public-basic.xml** - Public mode (HTTPS) with HTTP Basic Authentication
- **yahlp-public-google.xml** - Public mode (HTTPS) with Google OAuth2 Authentication
- **yahlp-public-entra.xml** - Public mode (HTTPS) with Microsoft Entra ID (Azure AD) OAuth2 Authentication

## Key Features

- **19 Integrated Services** - Radarr, Sonarr, Lidarr, Whisparr, Prowlarr, Jackett, Seerr, Bazarr, SABnzbd, NZBGet, NZBHydra, Transmission, qBittorrent, Deluge, Jellyfin, Plex, Emby, Tautulli, Maintainerr
- **4 Dashboard Styles** - Classic, Modern, Sleek, Minimal (with mobile-responsive layout)
- **Dark/Light Theme Toggle** - Persistent user preferences with theme persistence
- **Minimal Defaults** - All services disabled by default; users enable only what they need
- **Torrent/Usenet Links** - 15 pre-configured sites (torrent and usenet) with cached favicons
- **Multiple Authentication Methods** - None, Basic Auth, Google OAuth2, Microsoft Entra ID
- **Automatic HTTPS** - Let's Encrypt integration for public deployments
- **Subdomain Routing** - Support for media service subdomains in public mode
- **Additional vhost support** - map additional vhost files to the configuration to be served by the reverse proxy, without adding to the menu

## Getting Started

1. Choose a template based on your deployment mode:
   - **Private Network?** → Use `yahlp-private-basic.xml`
   - **Public with Passwords?** → Use `yahlp-public-basic.xml`
   - **Public with Google Accounts?** → Use `yahlp-public-google.xml`
   - **Public with Microsoft/Enterprise?** → Use `yahlp-public-entra.xml`

2. In Unraid, go to `Docker` → `Add Container` → `Select a template`

3. Load the template and configure your deployment settings

4. Enable the services you need and configure their backend URLs

## Documentation

- **Main Repository:** https://github.com/auskento/yahlp
- **Setup Guide:** See the main repository README for comprehensive setup and configuration instructions
- **Support:** Visit the main repository for issues, feature requests, and questions

## License

These templates are part of the YAHLP project. See the LICENSE file for details.
  </Profile>
  <Icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/auskento/yahlp/main/yahlp-150.png</Icon>
  <WebPage>https://github.com/auskento/yahlp-templates</WebPage>
  <Forum>https://forums.unraid.net/</Forum>
</CommunityApplications>
